# **Patrick Minero**

# Customer Service Professional

Focused customer service professional skilled in customer relationship development, team building and company performance. Accomplished in providing unsurpassed support to demanding customers. Offering eleven years of experience in related roles, as well as passion for always improving numbers, enhancing knowledge and exceeding expectations.

C	ont	ď	ct

#### **Address**

Ca N'oliva 13 - 17 Barcelona, B, 08020

#### **Phone**

346-777-79709

#### E-mail

patminero@outlook.com

## Skills

Team leadership and coaching

Excellent customer service skills

Goals and performance

Detail-oriented

Quality assurance

Technologically savvy

Coffee, beer and wine knowledge

Effective customer upselling

Process improvement

Issue and conflict resolution

Excellent multi-tasker

# **Work History**

2018-06 -2019-06

## Customer Service Representative.

Telus, International., Antiguo Cuscatlan, El Salvador., El Salvador

- Assisted in resolving customer's claims by providing great customer service.
- Constantly contacting vendors to schedule prompt service.
- Handled constant call load up to 70 calls per day while maintaining and exceeding company's KPI's.

2017-04 -2018-04

# **Supervisor**

Joinery Beerhall, Sausalito, California

- Oversee all daily service operations.
- Provide and assure great experience for all guest.
- Train and develop team members.
- Help general manager to set up cleaning schedules for staff.
- Balance cash flow after every shift.
- Handled work loads up to 400 guest per day.

### 2015-09 -2018-04

# Team Leader/Restaurant Server

Mill Valley Beerworks, Mill Valley, California

- Responsible for opening and closing procedures.
- Balanced cash intake at end of every shift.
- Training new team members, train team members with ever changing food and beverage menu
- Provide and assure guests with best experience possible.
- Kept daily check average over USD 40.

Languages		
Spanish	••••• Native	
English	••••• Native	
Italian	••○○○ Intermediate	

Languages

# 2015-01 Store Manager

Equator Coffees And Teas, Mill Valley, California

- This was the company's first retail cafe.
- Responsible to assure all day operations ran smoothly and provide great customer care.
- Hiring, training and development of employees.
- Labor, payroll, ordering, inventory and finances management.
- Built clientele for company's new venture.
- Exceeded company's store projections.

# **Education**

2005-03 - 2007-12	Some College (No Degree): Law		
	Central American University - La Libertad, El Salvador		
2001-01 - 2004-11	High School Diploma		
	Albert Einstein School - San Salvador, El Salvador		

# **Interests**

Yoga

Meditation

Computer Programming